[
    {
      "difficulty": "Easy",
      "xp": 10,
      "question": "1. What is 2 + 3?",
      "options": ["4", "5", "6", "7"],
      "answer": "5",
      "time": 30
    },
    {
      "difficulty": "Easy",
      "xp": 10,
      "question": "2. What is 1 + 6?",
      "options": ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
      "answer": "7",
      "time": 30
    },
    {
      "difficulty": "Easy",
      "xp": 10,
      "question": "3. What is 4 + 4?",
      "options": ["6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "answer": "8",
      "time": 30
    },
    {
      "difficulty": "Easy",
      "xp": 10,
      "question": "4. What is 5 + 2?",
      "options": ["6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "answer": "7",
      "time": 30
    },
    {
      "difficulty": "Easy",
      "xp": 10,
      "question": "5. What is 3 + 3?",
      "options": ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
      "answer": "6",
      "time": 30
    },
    {
      "difficulty": "Easy",
      "xp": 10,
      "question": "6. What is 6 + 1?",
      "options": ["6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "answer": "7",
      "time": 30
    },
    {
      "difficulty": "Easy",
      "xp": 10,
      "question": "7. What is 0 + 5?",
      "options": ["4", "5", "6", "7"],
      "answer": "5",
      "time": 30
    },
    {
      "difficulty": "Easy",
      "xp": 10,
      "question": "8. What is 2 + 4?",
      "options": ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
      "answer": "6",
      "time": 30
    },
    {
      "difficulty": "Easy",
      "xp": 10,
      "question": "9. What is 7 + 2?",
      "options": ["8", "9", "10", "11"],
      "answer": "9",
      "time": 30
    },
    {
      "difficulty": "Easy",
      "xp": 10,
      "question": "10. What is 9 + 0?",
      "options": ["8", "9", "10", "11"],
      "answer": "9",
      "time": 30
    }
  ]
  